{
    "id": "4ad4d4956a0e445c97cb91148224cd0a",
    "title": "Verbs Complementation Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Why are you ………………… me like that?",
            "description": "The verb look needs a preposition before its object.",
            "answers": [
                "looking",
                "look at",
                "looking at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aed19307e97f45dcb0f1eda6570780ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like you to ..................... this story.",
            "description": "The verb listen needs the preposition to before its object.",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "listen to",
                "hear to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2292fe26742b4ed288bffaf639646bcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s ………………. your plans.",
            "description": "The verb talk requires a preposition before its object. ",
            "answers": [
                "talk",
                "talk about",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51a1c61a696a4a57a2922a235b24e5b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s …………………. your plans.",
            "description": "The verb discuss does not take a preposition before its object.",
            "answers": [
                "discuss",
                "discuss about",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8ced48780b074385adc586654555db77"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. the station last night.",
            "description": "Usually a preposition is necessary before an expression of place.",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "arrived at",
                "arrived on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09ad9d8510974006960f202c5bf5942c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy …………………. cards.",
            "description": "The verb enjoy is followed by a noun or an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play",
                "to playing",
                "play"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f7b62425b8f447cb6f66c46ed3c7c0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I suggest …………………. an attorney.",
            "description": "The verb suggest cannot be followed by a to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "you to consult",
                "that you consult",
                "to consult",
                "that you to consult"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "64d52db09f854147b545c3b225da2d18"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police believe ………………… to be dangerous.",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object should be in its object form.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1e01c0b0be8843b1a22fae8b1adad035"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like you to explain .......................",
            "description": "The verb explain cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
            "answers": [
                "us your decision",
                "your decision to us",
                "your decision us"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e7fb5fbf4a34d5ebc3bd71032bee0c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you suggest …………………?",
            "description": "The verb suggest cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
            "answers": [
                "me a good cardiologist",
                "a good cardiologist to me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc7467693cfe45b3863fd14099f10736"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please describe …………………",
            "description": "The verb describe cannot be used with the structure indirect object + direct object.",
            "answers": [
                "us your new job",
                "your new job us",
                "your new job to us"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2fbd39b4462f445c8ae3f91347506bf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He fell ………………….",
            "description": "Fell off is an inseparable phrasal verb.",
            "answers": [
                "the ladder off",
                "off the ladder"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c97628e217264a968908c376e758432a"
        }
    ]
}